Artur Rodzinski Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1931-1976, bulk 1938-1953 (Box 1-11)
  - Chase, Richard G. see Massachusetts Indemnity Insurance Company
  - Chateau Elysée, 1950 (Box 2/37)
  - Chemical Bank and Trust Company (New York, N.Y.), 1951 (Box 2/38)
  - Chicago Friends of Symphony, n.d. (Box 2/39)
  - Chicago Musical College, 1949 (Box 2/40)
  - Chiesa, Miss., 1950 (Box 2/41)
  - Churchill, Winston, Sir, 1951 (Box 2/42)
  - Cia., 1949 (Box 2/43)
  - Cianfoni, D. Cesar, 1942-1943 (Box 2/44)
  - Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, 1947-1948 (Box 2/45)
  - City Center of Music and Drama (New York, N.Y.), 1944-1950 see also Violin Teachers Guild (Box 2/46)
  - Civic Symphony Society (Denver, Colo.), 1945 (Box 2/47)
  - Claflin, Avery, 1943 (Box 2/48)
  - Claire, Marion see Weber, Henry
  - Clark H. Getts, Inc., 1944 (Box 2/49)
  - Clark, W.A. Junior, 1930 (Box 2/50)
  - Clemens, Clara, 1935-1937 (Box 2/51)
  - Cleveland Institute of Music see Rubinstein, Beryl
  - Cleveland Orchestra, 1936-1953 (Box 2/52)
  - Coffy, John, n.d. (Box 2/53)
  - Cohen, Harriet, 1952 (Box 2/54)
  - Cole, Rossetter Gleason, 1942-1943 (Box 2/55)
  - Cole, Ulric, 1939 (Box 2/56)
  - Coleman, Frank A., 1947 (Box 2/57)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1944 (Box 2/58)
  - Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System), 1942-1946 (Box 2/59)
  - Columbia Graphophone Company (U.S.), 1948 (Box 2/60)
  - Columbia Recording Corporation see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Columbia Records, Inc., 1940-1951 see also Lieberson, Goddard (Box 2/61, 13/3)
  - Concert Management Arthur Judson, 1942-1944 (Box 2/62)
  - Concerts Symphoniques de Montréal, 1950-1953 (Box 2/63)
  - Conciertos Daniel see Sociedad Musical Daniel
  - Conciertos Zabaleta, 1950 (Box 2/64)
  - Confalone, Joe see Borós, Paul
  - Conoboy, LeRoy see Municipal Electric Plant
  - Continental Casualty Company see Massachusetts Indemnity Insurance Company
  - Copland, Aaron, 1943 (Box 2/65)
  - Coppicus, F.C. see Metropolitan Musical Bureau
  - Cordero, Roque, 1951 (Box 2/66)
  - Corker, Eve, 1951 (Box 2/67)
  - Coro, Armando J., 1949-1950 (Box 2/68)
  - Corti, Mario see Accademia di Santa Cecilia
  - Cosmos Travel Bureau, Inc., 1949 (Box 2/69)
  - Costanzo, Pasquale see Teatro di San Carlo
  - Cowell, Henry, 1945 (Box 2/70)
  - Cowles Magazines, Inc., 1949 (Box 2/71)
  - Cox, Mrs. Leonard see Cox, Sylvia van Rensselaer
  - Cox, Sylvia van Rensselaer, 1945 (Box 2/72)
  - Crandall, Mrs. R. Percy see George M. Horn Company
  - Crapski, B. Hutteu, 1948 (Box 2/73)
  - Creston, Paul, 1942-1946 (Box 2/74)
  - Crist, Bainbridge, 1943 (Box 2/75)
  - Crofoot, S. Elizabeth, 1942 (Box 2/76)
  - C miscellaneous, 1942-1949 (Box 2/77)
  - Dadant & Sons, 1942 (Box 3/1)
  - Daly, Michael L., 1943 (Box 3/2)
  - Danneman, Betty see Kahgan, Philip A. see Southern California Symphony Association
  - Datyner, Herman, 1950-1951 (Box 3/3)
  - Davies, Charles, n.d. (Box 3/4)
  - Davies, Joseph Edward, 1943 (Box 3/5)
  - Davies, Richbertg, Tydings, Beebe & Landa see Muriel Francis
  - D’Avignon, Francis W., 1951 (Box 3/6)
  - Davis, Edwina see Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System)
  - Davis, Jack C. see Muriel Francis
  - Davis, Wilfrid L. see Jack Adams and Co.
  - Davison, Martha Taylor, 1942 (Box 3/7)
  - Dawson, William Levi, 1943 (Box 3/8)
  - De Bebenedetti, Cecilia Benedit, 1950 (Box 3/9)
  - De Filippi, Amedeo, 1942 (Box 3/10)
  - De Gennaro, Mrs. M. see Mayfield & Mayfield
  - De Koos, G., 1948-1949 (Box 3/11)
  - De Meeus, Mrs. M., 1945 (Box 3/12)
  - De Rojas, Pascual see Patronato Pro-Música Sinfónica
  - De Sabata, Victor, 1952 (Box 3/13)
  - De Viteri Lafronte, Rosa see George M. Horn Company
  - DeGraff, Arthur C., 1951 (Box 3/14, 60/2)
  - Della Chiesa, Angelica, 1952 (Box 3/15)
  - Denecke, Julia, 1947 (Box 3/16)
  - Denecke, Mrs. Henry see Denecke, Julia
  - Denya, Marcelle, 1944 (Box 3/17)
  - Derqui, Guillermo P. Mackintosh see Argentina. Consulado General (New York, N.Y.)
  - DesRosiers, Marguerite see Concerts Symphoniques de Montréal
  - Devlin, Ann, n.d. (Box 3/18)
  - Diamond, David, 1941-1948 (Box 3/19)
  - Dicostanzo, 1951 (Box 3/20)
  - Dimitrovsky, A., 1943 (Box 3/21)
  - Dispeker, Thea see W. Colston Leigh, Inc.
  - Diton, Carl see Associated Negro Press
  - Dobrowen, Issay, 1938 (Box 3/22)
  - Dolan, Patrick see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Donkin, D.J.C., 1951 (Box 3/23)
  - Donnola, Frank J. see Liberty Music Shops, Inc.
  - Donohue, William M. see Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States
  - Doremus, Arthur L., 1944-1945 (Box 3/24)
  - Dorfmann, Ania, 1950 (Box 3/25)
  - Dow, Dorothy, 1950 (Box 3/26)
  - Dowling, Lyle see Oxford University Press
  - Downes, Irene see Downes, Olin
  - Downes, Olin, 1939-1957 see also National Symphony Orchestra Association (Washington, D.C.) (Box 3/27)
  - Driver, Tom Faw, 1943 (Box 3/28)
  - Drucker, Vlady, 1950 (Box 3/29)
  - Dufort, Ursula, 1951 (Box 3/30)
  - Dufy, Gaston see Images Musicales
  - Duke, Vernon, 1943-1948 (Box 3/31)
  - Dyer, Joseph H. Jr. see San Francisco (Calif.). Art Commission
  - Eardenson, Mrs. L. see Downes, Olin
  - Eames, Henry Purmort, 1942-1943 (Box 3/32)
  - Earle Ferris Company, 1946 (Box 3/33)
  - Edwards, Christine see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Eger, Joseph see New York Orchestral Society Inc.
  - Ehrenpreis, W.J., 1952 (Box 3/34)
  - Ehrman, Lillian May, 1944 (Box 3/35)
  - Elkan-Vogel Co., 1942 see also Jack Adams and Co. (Box 3/36)
  - Embassy of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics see Soviet Union. Posol’stvo (U.S.)
  - Emerson, Faith, 1942 (Box 3/37)
  - Ennis, Marcia see Ravinia Festival Association
  - Eppert, Carl, 1943 (Box 3/38)
  - Eppert, Hertha, 1945-1948 (Box 3/39)
  - Epstein, Maryi M., 1950 (Box 3/40)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, 1949-1953 (Box 3/41)
  - Escoe, Emanuel see Stern, Eskoe & Stern
  - Esser, Grace Denton see Music Academy of the West
  - Essex County Symphony Society, 1942-1948 (Box 3/42)
  - Etler, Alvin, 1948 (Box 3/43)
  - Evans, Bert, 1943-1944 (Box 3/44)
  - Evans, Wilbur see Galaxy Music Corporation
  - Eyer, Ronald F. see Musical America
  - Eyle, Felix, 1942-1950 (Box 3/45)
  - F.B. Ford Company see Ford, John B. Jr.
  - F.C. Taplin Company, 1942 (Box 3/46)
  - F.H. Turner & Co., 1942 (Box 3/47)
  - Farmers and Merchants National Bank of Los Angeles, 1949 (Box 3/48)
  - Fassett, James H. see Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.
  - Feine, Vivian, 1947 (Box 3/49)
  - Feist, Leonard see Mercury Music Corporation
  - Fekete, Zoltan, 1943 (Box 3/50)
  - Fele, 1951 (Box 3/51)
  - Ferraresi, Aldo, 1952 (Box 3/52)
  - Feuermann, Emanuel, 1941 (Box 3/53)
  - Field, Joseph, 1945 (Box 3/54)
  - Field, Marshall see Simkhovitch, Mary Kingsbury
  - Filarmonica see Sociedad Musical Daniel
  - Fine, Vivian, 1947 (Box 3/55)
  - Finzi, Ada, 1949-1951 see also Biennale di Venezia (Box 3/56)
  - Finzi, Ada, 1952-1953 see also Biennale di Venezia (Box 3/57)
  - Fitch, Edith, 1949 see also Stern, Escoe & Stern (Box 3/58)
  - Fitelberg, Jerzy, 1937-1947 (Box 3/59)
  - Fitelberg, Tamara, 1937 (Box 3/60)
  - Fitelson and Mayers, 1934-1935 (Box 3/61)
  - Fitelson, H. William see Fitelson and Mayers
  - Flagg, Richard B., 1951 (Box 3/62)
  - Flagstad, Kirsten, 1950 (Box 3/63)
  - Fletcher, Grant, 1947 (Box 3/64)
  - Ford, Hazel Hopkins, 1949 (Box 3/65)
  - Ford, John B. Jr., n.d. (Box 3/66)
  - Forkner, Claude Ellis, 1949-1951 (Box 3/67)
  - Foss, Lukas, 1944-1954 (Box 3/68)
  - Foster, George A. see New Orleans Symphony Society
  - Foster, H.P. see Liberty Mutual Insurance Company
  - Fox, Mrs. Paul J. see Polish Arts Club
  - Fraenkel, Bessie Bartlett, 1942, 1950 (Box 3/69)
  - Francis, Muriel see Muriel Francis
  - Frank, Marco, 1945 (Box 3/70)
  - Frank S. Hartley Jewels, 1949 (Box 3/71)
  - Frankel, Cecil see Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States see Sturdy, L. Alice
  - Frankenstein, Alfred Victor see San Francisco Chronicle see San Francisco (Calif.). Art Commission
  - Franklin, F. see Franklin Typewriter Service
  - Franklin Typewriter Service, 1949 (Box 3/73)
  - Franze, Johannes see Teatro Colón (Buenos Aires, Argentina)
  - Frederiksen, Sigurd, 1943 (Box 3/74)
  - Freeman, Jay C. see Rudolph Wurlitzer Company
  - Freitag, Trude see Rychtarik, Richard
  - Frey, Louise see New York Philharmonic
  - Friedberg, Carl, 1950 (Box 3/75)
  - Friedgut, Harry see City Center of Music and Drama (New York, N.Y.) see Essex County Symphony Society
  - Frischler, Erica see Frischler, Hermann
  - Frischler, Heinz see Frischler, Hermann
  - Frischler, Hermann, 1951 (Box 3/76)
  - Fuchs, Josef, 1945 (Box 3/77)
  - Fuleihan, Anis, 1944-1945 (Box 3/78)
  - Fust, Joseph, 1950 (Box 3/79)
  - Fziki, n.d. (Box 3/80)
  - F miscellaneous, 1950-1953 (Box 3/81)
  - G. Ricordi & Co., 1950 (Box 3/82)
  - G. Schirmer, Inc., 1942-1951 (Box 3/83)
  - Gabrilowitsch, Clara see Clemens, Clara
  - Gabrilowitsch, Ossip, 1933-1935 (Box 3/84)
  - Galaxy Music Corporation, 1947 (Box 3/85)
  - Galeen, Henrik, 1945 (Box 3/86)
  - Gamsjäger, Rudolf, 1952 (Box 3/87)
  - Ganz, Rudolph, 1943-1947 (Box 3/88)
  - Garbousova, Raya, 1945-1946 (Box 3/89)
  - Gardner, Samuel, 1945 (Box 3/90)
  - Gehle, Frederick W. see United States. War Finance Division
  - Geiger, Robert C., 1947 (Box 4/1)
  - General Electric Company. Lamp Dept., 1942 (Box 4/2)
  - General Electric X-Ray Corporation, 1942 (Box 4/3)
  - General Motors Corporation. Cadillac Motor Car Division, 1949 (Box 4/4)
  - Genia, 1951 (Box 4/5)
  - George, Earl, n.d. (Box 4/6)
  - George M. Horn Company, 1949 (Box 4/7)
  - Gesensway, Louis, 1943 (Box 4/8)
  - Ghedini, Giorgio Federico see Angelicum dei Frati Minori
  - Gibson, Francis P., 1944 (Box 4/9)
  - Gibson, Gordon, 1942 (Box 4/10)
  - Gilbert, Helen, 1945 (Box 4/11)
  - Gilbert, Richard see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Gilman, Lawrence, 1937 (Box 4/12)
  - Gimpel, Jakob, 1943-1944 (Box 4/13)
  - Gingold, George see Gingold, Josef
  - Gingold, Gladys see Gingold, Josef
  - Gingold, Josef, 1949 (Box 4/14)
  - Giulini, Leopoldo see Angelicum dei Frati Minori
  - Glenn, Carroll, 1942 (Box 4/15)
  - Goberman, Max, 1943 (Box 4/16)
  - Gold, Ernest, 1943 see also Mills Music, Inc. (Box 4/17)
  - Goldberg, Albert see Los Angeles Times
  - Goldfuss, Abraham, 1942 (Box 4/18)
  - Goldie, Arthur, 1944 (Box 4/19)
  - Goldovsky, Boris, n.d. (Box 4/20)
  - Goldsmith, B.A. see Henri Stern Watch Agency, Inc.
  - Golschmann, Vladimir, 1938-1949 (Box 4/21)
  - González, Ramón, 1944 (Box 4/22)
  - Goodyear Aircraft Corporation, 1943 (Box 4/23)
  - Goossens, Eugene, Sir, 1938-1946 (Box 4/24, 61/3)
  - Gould, Morton see Mills Music, Inc.
  - Graene, Jack, 1944 (Box 4/25)
  - Graf, Herbert, 1939 (Box 4/26)
  - Grant, Margaret see Berkshire Music Center
  - Gravely Manufacturing Co., 1942 (Box 4/27)
  - Great Britain. Embassy (U.S.), 1944 (Box 4/28)
  - Green, C. Alfin see Pan American World Airways, Inc.
  - Green, Ray, 1945-1948 (Box 4/29)
  - Greenbaum, Wolff & Ernst, 1949-1952 (Box 4/30)
  - Greene, Lorenzo Johnston, 1943 (Box 4/31)
  - Greimer, A.W. see Steinway & Sons
  - Greinert, E. see Stadium Concerts, Inc.
  - Greissle, Felix see G. Schirmer, Inc.
  - Grey, Robert G., 1940-1945 (Box 4/32)
  - Griffeth, Merle R., 1943 (Box 4/33)
  - Griffis, Stanton see United States. Foreign Service
  - Griffith, Kenneth, 1942 (Box 4/34)
  - Griffith, Lena see Essex County Symphony Society
  - Grigg, Barbara see Time, Inc.
  - Grilli, Marcel see Nihon Hōsō Kyōkai
  - Gronowetter, Freda, 1945 (Box 4/35)
  - Gross, Bethuel, 1942 (Box 4/36)
  - Gross, Ludwik see DeGraff, Arthur C.
  - Gross, Robert, 1945 (Box 4/37)
  - Grove, Anheli see Sztark, H. and A.
  - Grunes, David J. see Am-Rus Music Corporation
  - Guggenberg, Markus von, 1952 (Box 4/38)
  - Guggenheimer, Minnie Schafer, 1944 (Box 4/39)
  - Guggenheimer, Mrs. Harles S. see Guggenheimer, Minnie Schafer
  - Gump, H. N. see Clark H. Getts, Inc.
  - Guthrie, James K., 1936-1947 (Box 4/40)
  - G miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 4/41)
  - Haas, Alexander F. see San Francisco (Calif.). Art Commission
  - Hadley, Henry Kimball, 1934 (Box 4/42)
  - Haensel & Jones, 1942-1945 see also Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System) (Box 4/43)
  - Hageman, Richard, 1938-1943 (Box 4/44)
  - Hahn, Edgar A. see Mooney, Hahn, Loeser, Keough & Freedheim
  - Haieff, Alexei, 1943 (Box 4/45)
  - Halász, László see City Center of Music and Drama (New York, N.Y.)
  - Haley, Thomas J. see New York (City). Dept. of Finance
  - Halifax, [Edward Frederick Lindley Wood, Earl of] see Great Britain. Embassy (U.S.)
  - Hall, David see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Halusza, Riki, 1951 (Box 4/46)
  - Hammer, Heinrich, 1944-1947 (Box 4/47)
  - Handler, Nathan E., 1945 (Box 4/48)
  - Hansen, Katherine see Music Teachers’ Quarterly
  - Hanson, Howard, 1945 (Box 4/49)
  - Hanzl, Rudolf see Wiener Philharmoniker
  - Happ, Eugene see South Bend Symphony Orchestra
  - Harold Holt, Ltd., 1949-1950 (Box 4/50)
  - Harp, Raleigh see Carnegie Hall Recording Co.
  - Harris, Johana see Harris, Roy
  - Harris, Roy, 1936-1948 see also Gingold, Josef (Box 4/51)
  - Harry Smith Recordings, 1942 (Box 4/52)
  - Harty, Hamilton, Sir, 1935 (Box 4/53)
  - Hartzog, H.H. see A.I. Root Company
  - Harvey, Russell, 1943 (Box 4/54)
  - Haubiel, Charles, 1942-1945 (Box 4/55)
  - Hauser, Arthur A. see Carl Fischer Inc.
  - Havener, Helen see National Federation of Music Clubs
  - Hawkes, Ralph see Boosey & Hawkes Inc.
  - Haynes, Nita, n.d. (Box 4/56)
  - Hays, C. Lansing Jr. see Leve, Hecht, Hadfield & McAlpin
  - Hays, Will Harrison see Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America
  - Hearst, Siegfried see National Concert and Artists Corporation
  - Heilner, Irwin, 1944-1945 (Box 4/57)
  - Heinsheimer, Hans W. see Boosey & Hawkes Inc. see Boosey, Hawkes, Belwin Inc. see G. Schirmer, Inc.
  - Heller, Gesine see Simkhovitch, Mary Kingsbury
  - Hendl, Walter, 1945-1951 (Box 4/58)
  - Henri Stern Watch Agency, Inc., 1949 (Box 4/59)
  - Henry Holt and Company, 1950 (Box 4/60)
  - Hernández, Leopoldo, 1950-1951 (Box 4/61)
  - Herou, Karl-Thore, 1951 (Box 4/62)
  - Hess, Harold F., 1943-1944 (Box 4/63)
  - Hicks, George Raymond, 1945 (Box 4/64)
  - Hier, Ethel Glenn, 1945 (Box 4/65)
  - Higgins, Grover, 1942 (Box 4/66)
  - Hite, George E. Jr. see Milbank, Tweed, Hope & Hadley
  - Hoffman, Earl, 1947 (Box 4/67)
  - Hoffman, Irwin, 1945 (Box 4/68)
  - Hofmann, Josef, 1936-1937 (Box 4/69)
  - Hogg, Ima see Houston Symphony Society
  - Holbrooke, Dan, 1948-1949 (Box 4/70)
  - Hollywood Bowl Association, 1949-1951 see also Southern California Symphony Association (Box 4/71)
  - Holt, Harold see Harold Holt, Ltd.
  - Hope Associates see Earle Ferris Company
  - Hope, Constance see Radio Corporation of America. RCA Victor Division
  - Horenstein, Jascha, 1943 (Box 4/72)
  - Hornblower & Weeks, 1942-1949 (Box 4/73)
  - Houston Symphony Society, 1947 (Box 4/74)
  - Hoving, Walter, 1944 (Box 4/75)
  - Huber, Frederick, 1942 (Box 4/76)
  - Huberman, Bronislaw, 1935-1936 (Box 4/77)
  - Hubert, Marcel, 1944 (Box 4/78)
  - Hugh, Ross, 1945 (Box 4/79)
  - Hughes, Adella Prentiss, 1942 (Box 4/80)
  - Hughes, Mrs. see Pettis, Ashley
  - Hull, Helen, 1945-1946 (Box 4/81)
  - Hurd, Frederick see Brundage, Story and Rose
  - Hutcheson, Irmgart, 1937 (Box 4/82)
  - Hyndman, R.V. see G. Schirmer, Inc.
  - H miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 4/83)
  - Il Sindaco di Firenze see La Pira, Giorgio
  - Images Musicales, 1947-1948 (Box 4/84)
  - Imparato, Giovanni, 1949 (Box 4/85)
  - Incisoria Dischi see Alberto, Pisani
  - Insana, Silvio, 1947 (Box 4/86)
  - Internal Revenue Agent in Charge, 1942 (Box 4/87)
  - International Exposition of the Arts see Nabokov, Nicolas
  - Irish, Mrs. Leiland Atherton see Southern California Symphony Association
  - Isham & Isham, 1949-1950 (Box 4/88)
  - Isham, Robert F. see Isham & Isham
  - Jabs, Russell, E., n.d. (Box 4/89)
  - Jachimowicz, Jan, 1951 (Box 4/90)
  - Jack Adams and Co., 1948-1950 (Box 4/91, 60/3)
  - Jacobi, Frederick, 1943 (Box 5/1)
  - Jacobs, Ivan, 1945 (Box 5/2)
  - Jaffe & Stern, 1953 (Box 5/3)
  - Jaffin, Theodore S. see Greenbaum, Wolff & Ernst
  - Jafke, Orville W., 1951 (Box 5/4)
  - Jarmel, Dorle see National Federation of Music Clubs
  - Jelliffe, Rowena Woodham see Karamu House
  - John F. White, Inc., 1949 (Box 5/5)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1945 (Box 5/6)
  - Johnson, Thor, 1943-1945 see also Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra (Box 5/7)
  - Jones, Isabel Morse, 1950 (Box 5/8)
  - Jones, Mrs. T. Catesby, 1943 (Box 5/9)
  - Jospe, Erwin, 1945 (Box 5/10)
  - Judd, G.E. see Boston Symphony Orchestra
  - Judson, Arthur see Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System) see Concert Management Arthur Judson see New York Philharmonic see Simkhovitch, Mary Kingsbury
  - Juilliard School of Music, 1949-1950 (Box 5/11)
  - Jurres, André see Stichting Donemus
  - Kachouk, Michel, 1949 (Box 5/12)
  - Kahgan, Philip A., 1949 (Box 5/13)
  - Kahn, Erminie, 1944-1945 (Box 5/14)
  - Kappel, Gertrude, 1936 (Box 5/15)
  - Karamu House, 1942 (Box 5/16)
  - Kastner, Alfred, 1945 (Box 5/17)
  - Kaston, Henryk, 1942 (Box 5/18)
  - Kaston, Maryna, n.d. (Box 5/19)
  - Kaufman, Louis, 1945 (Box 5/20)
  - Kaufman, Schima, 1944 (Box 5/21)
  - Kay, Ulysses, 1947 (Box 5/22)
  - Kaye, Bess W. see American Music Center (New York, N.Y.)
  - Kaye, S. A., 1952 (Box 5/23)
  - Kazu, 1951 (Box 5/24)
  - Keller, Felicitas see Sociedad Musical Daniel
  - Kenna, Gilbert, 1942 (Box 5/25)
  - Kenneth Allen Associates, Inc., 1953 (Box 5/26)
  - Kenyon, Doris, 1938 (Box 5/27)
  - Kerby, Elvira see G. Ricordi & Co.
  - Kern, Imre, 1949 (Box 5/28)
  - Kerr, Jessie, 1949 (Box 5/29)
  - Kerr, Muriel, 1945 (Box 5/30)
  - Khalatov, Semen see Soviet Union. Posol’stvo (U.S.)
  - Kilbane, M.A. see Vosburgh, Carl J.
  - Kinander, Robert, 1949 (Box 5/31)
  - Kinandr, Margaret, 1949 (Box 5/32)
  - Kindler, Hans see National Symphony Orchestra Association (Washington, D.C.)
  - Kircher, Halite see Luchini, F.
  - Kisch, Royalton, 1948 (Box 5/33)
  - Klaerchen, 1949 (Box 5/34)
  - Klyor, Victor I., 1942 (Box 5/35)
  - Knight, F.M. see Ravinia Festival Association
  - Kohs, Ellis B., 1947 (Box 5/36)
  - Kolberg, Hugo, 1945-1950 (Box 5/37)
  - Kondracki, Michal, 1945 (Box 5/38)
  - Konovalov, Mr. see Radamsky, Sergei
  - Konrad, Robert, 1942 (Box 5/39)
  - Konzert-Direktion Hans Adler, 1951-1953 (Box 5/40)
  - Kopp, Leo L., 1949 (Box 5/41)
  - Korn, Richard, 1946 (Box 5/42)
  - Korolewicz-Waydowa, Janina, 1935 (Box 5/43)
  - Korotkin, Fred, 1942, One photograph of Korotkin with his collection of photographs of famous people. (Box 5/44)
  - Koshetz, Marina, 1944-1949 (Box 5/45)
  - Kosmetos, John, 1942-1945 (Box 5/46)
  - Kostelanetz, Andre, 1945 (Box 5/47)
  - Kotkowski, Gustavo, 1950 (Box 5/48)
  - Koudriavtzeff, Nicolas see Canadian Concerts and Artists
  - Koussevitzky, Serge, 1945-1949 (Box 5/49)
  - Koutzen, Boris, 1943 (Box 5/50)
  - Krasoff, Wanda, 1950 (Box 5/51)
  - Krehm, Ida, 1944-1951 (Box 5/52)
  - Kreutz, Arthur, 1943-1945 (Box 5/53)
  - Krueger, Karl, 1938-1949 (Box 5/54)
  - Krymskaia A.S.S.R. (R.S.F.S.R.). Narodnyĭ komissariat prosveshcheniia, 1934 (Box 5/55)
  - Kuhn, Mrs., n.d. (Box 5/56)
  - Kunze, Otto see Marionette Productions
  - Kurenko, Maria, 1944 (Box 5/57)
  - Kurtz, Efrem see Earle Ferris Company
  - Kuypers, Mr. see Harris, Roy
  - Kvasnes, n.d. (Box 5/58)
  - Kyne, Alice, 1944 see also Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System) see also Haensel & Jones see also New York Committee of the National War Fund see also Webster, Mrs. N.C. (Box 5/59)
  - La Pira, Giorgio, 1954 (Box 5/60)
  - LaBerge, Bernard R. see Boosey & Hawkes Inc.
  - Labunski, Felix, 1943-1946 (Box 5/61)
  - Lafronte, Rosa de Viteri see George M. Horn Company
  - Lagodzinski, Teofil S. see Pulaski Day Memorial Committee
  - Lake Placid Drama Festival see Piscator, Erwin
  - Lake Placid Hardward Co., Inc. see Lake Placid Plumbing & Heating Co.
  - Lake Placid (N.Y.), 1949-1950 (Box 5/62)
  - Lake Placid Plumbing & Heating Co., 1949 (Box 5/63)
  - Lamkoff, Paul, 1948 (Box 5/64)
  - Lane, Martin B., 1942 (Box 5/65)
  - Larry Allen, Inc. see Music Corporation of America
  - Lasek, K., 1948 (Box 5/66)
  - Lasker, Doris Kenyon see Kenyon, Doris
  - Lauterbach, Otto, 1942 (Box 5/67)
  - Law offices of Howard E. Reinheimer, 1942 (Box 5/68)
  - Law offices of Harold R. Soden, 1949 see also Proskauer, Rose, Goetz & Mendelsohn (Box 5/69)
  - Lawrence Evans Artist Management, Inc. see Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System)
  - Lawrence, Robert, 1965 (Box 5/70)
  - Lazăr, Filip, 1934 (Box 5/71)
  - Lazare, P. see M. Baron Co.
  - Lea see Beu
  - Lease, Marvin, 1942 (Box 5/72)
  - LeBrasseur & Oakley, 1949 (Box 5/73)
  - Lee, Dai-Keong, 1940-1948 (Box 5/74)
  - Lee, Everett, 1949 (Box 5/75)
  - Lees, Benjamin, 1953-1970 (Box 5/76)
  - Leff, David D., 1942 (Box 5/77)
  - Legrand, O. see Leningradskaia gosudarstvennaia filarmoniia
  - Lehman Radio Salon, 1951 (Box 5/78)
  - Leiser, Henri see William Morris Agency
  - Leningrad Philharmonic see Leningradskaia gosudarstvennaia filarmoniia
  - Leningradskaia gosudarstvennaia filarmoniia, 1934 (Box 5/79)
  - Leschke, Hans, 1950 (Box 5/80)
  - Leve, Hecht, Hadfield & McAlpin, 1950-1951 (Box 5/81)
  - Levenson, David M., 1942 (Box 5/82)
  - Levicoff, Pearl R., 1944 (Box 5/83)
  - Levin, Harold H. see Proskauer, Rose, Goetz & Mendelsohn
  - Levin, Sylvan, 1935 (Box 5/84)
  - Levine, Marks see Maier, Guy see National Concert and Artists Corporation
  - Levy, Joseph L., 1950 (Box 5/85)
  - Levy, Mrs. Joseph see Hollywood Bowl Association
  - Lewando, Ralph, 1949 (Box 5/86)
  - Lhevinne, Rosina, 1944 (Box 5/87)
  - Liberson, Ryessa D. see Vsesoiuznoe obshchestvo kul’turnoĭ sviazi s zagranitseĭ (Soviet Union)
  - Liberty Music Shops, Inc., 1953 (Box 5/88)
  - Liberty Mutual Insurance Company, 1942 (Box 5/89)
  - Liberty United Department see Liberty Mutual Insurance Company
  - Libidins, David see Zirato, Bruno
  - Lieberson, Goddard, 1942-1945 see also Robeson, Paul see also Russian War Relief, Inc. (Box 5/90)
  - Lieberson, Goddard, 1946-1953 see also Robeson, Paul see also Russian War Relief, Inc. (Box 5/91)
  - Life, 1949 (Box 6/1)
  - Lilien, Ignace, 1947-1951 (Box 6/2)
  - Lilleback, Anne G., 1949 (Box 6/3)
  - Lily, Herbert D., 1942 (Box 6/4)
  - Lincer, Mary, 1943 (Box 6/5)
  - Lincer, William, 1943 (Box 6/6)
  - Liong, Hock, 1951 (Box 6/7)
  - Lipkin, Arthur Bennett, 1936-1942 (Box 6/8)
  - Lipstone, Lousi R., 1949 (Box 6/9)
  - Lira Espejo, Eduardo see Conciertos Zabaleta
  - Littledale, Clara Savage see Muriel Francis
  - Litvinoff, Maxim see Soviet Union. Posol’stvo (U.S.)
  - Lobenstein, Irmengard see Rot-Weiss-Rot
  - Lockwood, Normand, 1938-1943 (Box 6/10)
  - Loesser, n.d. (Box 6/11)
  - Long, Johnny, 1944 (Box 6/12)
  - Loomis, Clarence, 1945 (Box 6/13)
  - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai, 1943-1947 (Box 6/14)
  - Lord, G. Frank see Wheeler & Taylor, Inc.
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra, 1949-1951 (Box 6/15)
  - Los Angeles Times, 1949 (Box 6/16)
  - Lóska, 1945 (Box 6/17)
  - Lotish, J.D. see Amkniga Corporation
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1953 (Box 6/18)
  - Luchini, F., 1952 (Box 6/19)
  - Lustig, Ludwig, 1949-1950 (Box 6/20)
  - Lynn, Nora, 1949 (Box 6/21)
  - Lyons, Edna, 1945 (Box 6/22)
  - L miscellaneous, 1943-1950 (Box 6/23)
  - M. Baron Co., 1942 (Box 6/24)
  - M. Steinert & Sons, 1942 (Box 6/25)
  - Maazel, Marvin, 1953 (Box 6/26)
  - Maciejewski, Roman, 1945 (Box 6/27)
  - MacKinnon, Douglas A. see Armed Forces Master Records, Inc.
  - Maesch, L.K., 1942-1943 (Box 6/28)
  - Magaloff, Nikita, 1950 (Box 6/29)
  - Maggio musicale fiorentino, 1951-1952 see also Radio audizioni Italia (Box 6/30)
  - Magin, James Ch. H., 1945 (Box 6/31)
  - Maier, Guy, 1942 (Box 6/32)